Philip K. Crowe Papers MS109
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1953 -- 1975; 1950 -- 1975; MS109.001; 32.4 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence: Scl-Sco, MS109.001.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scof-Scott, MS109.001.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scott-Scott, MS109.001.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scott-Scott, MS109.001.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scott-Scott, MS109.001.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scott-Scott, MS109.001.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scranton, MS109.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scribner, MS109.001.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scribner, MS109.001.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scribner, MS109.001.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scribner, MS109.001.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scribner, MS109.001.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Scull, MS109.001.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence: Seabrook, MS109.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Sei-Sel, MS109.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Selving, MS109.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Sem, MS109.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Senate of the U.S., MS109.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Sha-Sha, MS109.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: She-She, MS109.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Shi-Shu, MS109.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Sim-Sind, MS109.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Skj-Slaw, MS109.001.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Smith, MS109.001.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Smith, MS109.001.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Smith, MS109.001.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Smith, MS109.001.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Sny-Social, MS109.001.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Society of Colonial Wars, MS109.001.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Soulbury, MS109.001.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Soulbury, MS109.001.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Soulbury, MS109.001.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - South Africa, MS109.001.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - South Africa, MS109.001.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Spivey-Speeches, MS109.001.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Squires-Stoessel, MS109.001.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Stor-Storh, MS109.001.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Thomas-Topping, MS109.001.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence: Ste-Sten, MS109.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Stil-Stir, MS109.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Stra-Stre, MS109.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Str-Str, MS109.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Str-Str, MS109.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Su-Suh, MS109.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Sulzberger, MS109.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Sva-Sve, MS109.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Swift-Swin, MS109.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Travel, MS109.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Aarhus (weekend with Flemming Juncker), 1904 -- 1975; MS109.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Aalborg, 1904 -- 1974; MS109.001.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Alesund, Andalsnes, Molde, Kristiansund, and Trondheim, 1969; MS109.001.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Amb. Crowe, MS109.001.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Arctic Express, 1970; MS109.001.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Bergen, Havgesund, and Stavanger, 1969; MS109.001.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Bergen, 1970; MS109.001.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Berlin and East Berlin, 1975; MS109.001.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Berlin, 1972; MS109.001.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Cancelled trip to Bhutan, 1973; MS109.001.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Cancelled hunting trip to Bornholm, 1974; MS109.001.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Bornholm (Buck shooting), 1974; MS109.001.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Bornholm, 1975; MS109.001.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Bornholm, 1974; MS109.001.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Cancelled trip to Brussels, 1974; MS109.001.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Brussels, 1975; MS109.001.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Brussels, NATO Central Command, and The Hague, 1971; MS109.001.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Brussels (Control: Mr. Hennemeyer), 1969; MS109.001.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Cancelled trip to Bulgaria, 1910 -- 1974; MS109.001.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Canary Islands-Cancelled, 1973; MS109.001.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Canary Islands-Cancelled, 1972; MS109.001.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Chiefs of Mission Conference, 1911 -- 1969; MS109.001.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Copenhagen, 1970; MS109.001.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Dahomey, 1908 -- 1972; MS109.001.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Dip. Corps Trip, 1974; MS109.001.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Dombas, 1969; MS109.001.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Faroes, 1974; MS109.001.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Flam (with Mr. Myhre), 1971; MS109.001.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fon Off trip for Dip Corps, 1973; MS109.001.020.00039 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Funen and Southern Jutland (Funen Home Guard), 1974; MS109.001.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Em River, Sweden, 1972; MS109.001.020.00041 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Em River, Sweden, 1975; MS109.001.020.00042 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Em River, 1974; MS109.001.020.00043 (Box 20)
  - Travel: England (Norwich), 1972; MS109.001.020.00044 (Box 20)
  - Travel: England-Shooting, 1972; MS109.001.020.00045 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Ente River, 1972; MS109.001.020.00046 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Alta River-Fishing-Evening, 1970; MS109.001.020.00047 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Aurland River (Ohnstad Beat), 1972; MS109.001.020.00048 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Etne River, 1971; MS109.001.020.00049 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Gaula(r) River, 1905 -- 1972; MS109.001.020.00050 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Gaula River, Flam River, Roros, 1970 -- 1972; MS109.001.020.00051 (Box 20)
    Gaula River, June 6-8, Flam River, June 9-11, Roros, June 12-14. Date Range is Approximate.
  - Travel: Fishing (Laerdal and Namsen Rivers), 1971; MS109.001.020.00052 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing- Vosso River, Driva River, Rauma River, 1906 -- 1970; MS109.001.020.00053 (Box 20)
    Vosso River, June 30-July 4, Driva River, July 5-11, Rauma River, July 13-15, 1970.
  - Travel: Fishing- Driva River, 1971; MS109.001.020.00054 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing- Hemsedal, Laerdal, 1906 -- 1970; MS109.001.020.00055 (Box 20)
    Hemsedal, June 4-7, Laerdal, June 7-9, 1970.
  - Travel: Fishing- Vosso River, 1970; MS109.001.020.00056 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Laerdal-cancelled, 1908 -- 1972; MS109.001.020.00057 (Box 20)
    August 1-3 or 29-31, 1972.
  - Travel: Fishing on Suldal River, 1972; MS109.001.020.00058 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing (with Mr. Ragnar Platou), 1971; MS109.001.020.00059 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing in Iceland-cancelled, 1908 -- 1971; MS109.001.020.00060 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing-Malselv Pool-cancelled, 1970 -- 1972; MS109.001.020.00061 (Box 20)
    August 31-September 1. Dates are approximate.
  - Travel: Fishing in Spain-cancelled, 1973; MS109.001.020.00062 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing in Spain, 1972; MS109.001.020.00063 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing-Driva River, 1972; MS109.001.020.00064 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing on Vosso River, 1972; MS109.001.020.00065 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing Forde, 1973; MS109.001.020.00066 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing Gaular, 1973; MS109.001.020.00067 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing with Mr. Terkelsen on Omme River, 1975; MS109.001.020.00068 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing in Sweden, 1971; MS109.001.020.00069 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing-Molde, Driva, and Stryn, 1973; MS109.001.020.00070 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Fishing with Mr. Terkelsen, 1974; MS109.001.020.00071 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Garmisch-Epsilon 72, 1972; MS109.001.020.00072 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Germany with Hagerty & Col. Cooper, 1971; MS109.001.020.00073 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Germany-cancelled, 1970; MS109.001.020.00074 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Glen, Sweden with Mr. Cappelen, 1971; MS109.001.020.00075 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Greece, 1975; MS109.001.020.00076 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Greece and Israel, 1972; MS109.001.020.00077 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Greenland, 1974; MS109.001.020.00078 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Gyldensteen, Steensballegaard, 1974; MS109.001.020.00079 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Hamar and Lillehammer, 1970; MS109.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Heidelberg (Briefings and Boar Shooting), 1974; MS109.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Heidelberg-Germany, 1972; MS109.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Helsinki (Speech at Finnish-Am Society), 1974; MS109.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Helsinki for Nordic Ambs Conference, 1972; MS109.001.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Travel: to farm of Judge and Mrs. Hohle-cancelled, 1971; MS109.001.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Grouse shooting at Grindaheim, Hunting with Mr. Treschow at Harangervidda-cancelled, 1909 -- 1971; MS109.001.021.00007 (Box 21)
    Grouse shooting at Grindaheim, September 14-17, Hunting with Mr. Treschow at Harangervidda-cancelled, September 18-25, 1971.
  - Travel: Hunting (Moose) with Mr. Treschow, 1909 -- 1972; MS109.001.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Hunting in Hungary, 1972; MS109.001.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Hunting in Poland, 1971; MS109.001.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Eidsvoll-Hunting, 1971; MS109.001.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Hunting in Bulgaria-cancelled, 1972; MS109.001.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Hunting at Dombas and Grindaheim, 1909 -- 1970; MS109.001.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Hunting (Mr. Mogens Harttung and Count Bernstorff), 1973; MS109.001.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - Travel: International Atlantic Salmon Foundation Meeting-London, 1911 -- 1970; MS109.001.021.00015 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Jan Mayen, 1907 -- 1972; MS109.001.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Kiel and Whalstorf, 1975; MS109.001.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Kristiansund (N) and Surrounding Islands, 1971; MS109.001.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Lake Mjosa-cancelled, 1971; MS109.001.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Larvik for Pheasant Shooting with Mr. Treschow, 1972; MS109.001.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Larvik (Farms of Mr. Treschow), 1971; MS109.001.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Leningrad, Stockholm (Scan Chfs of Mission Meeting), 1905 -- 1975; MS109.001.021.00022 (Box 21)
    Leningrad, May 7-11, Stockholm, May 11-13, 1975.
  - Travel: Lofotens and North, 1970; MS109.001.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London, 1970; MS109.001.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London (Gen. Taute), Stuttgart (Capt. Coulthard), 1969; MS109.001.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London, 1910 -- 1974; MS109.001.021.00026 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London-cancelled, 1975; MS109.001.021.00027 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London, Second Int'l WWF Congress, 1970; MS109.001.021.00028 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London and the U.S., 1973 -- 1974; MS109.001.021.00029 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London, 1970; MS109.001.021.00030 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London-cancelled, 1973; MS109.001.021.00031 (Box 21)
  - Travel: London, Hebrides, and then Grouse Shooting, 1971; MS109.001.021.00032 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Morges, Switzerland, 1971; MS109.001.021.00033 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Murmansk, 1972; MS109.001.021.00034 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Naples and London, 1971; MS109.001.021.00035 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Naples and Rome, 1975; MS109.001.021.00036 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Narvik and Harstad, 1970; MS109.001.021.00037 (Box 21)
  - Travel: North Norway, 1969; MS109.001.021.00038 (Box 21)
  - Travel: North Norway and Lofotens, 1972; MS109.001.021.00039 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Norway (Fishing on Driva River), 1975; MS109.001.021.00040 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Norway, Kristiansand (S), 1974; MS109.001.021.00041 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Norwegian Sea (Capt. Coulthard), 1971; MS109.001.021.00042 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Oslo, 1974; MS109.001.021.00043 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Paris, Int'l Fario Club-Amb. cancelled out, 1911 -- 1973; MS109.001.021.00044 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Paris, 1971; MS109.001.021.00045 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Rebild, 1974; MS109.001.021.00046 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Reykjavik, 1970; MS109.001.021.00047 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Romania, 1972; MS109.001.021.00048 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Roros, 1971; MS109.001.021.00049 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Salzburg, Austria-cancelled, 1908 -- 1975; MS109.001.021.00050 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Sandnes (with Mr. Ausland), 1971; MS109.001.021.00051 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Shooting with Count and Countess Wedell, 1973; MS109.001.021.00052 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Shooting with Carsten Brunn, 1972; MS109.001.021.00053 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Shooting with Mathiesen at Skabland, 1970; MS109.001.021.00054 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Pheasant Shooting with Count Lewenhaupt, 1971; MS109.001.021.00055 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Reindeer Shooting with Mr. Poulsson-cancelled, 1971; MS109.001.021.00056 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Soro, Nykobing Falster, Humble, 1974; MS109.001.021.00057 (Box 21)
  - Travel: South Norway, 1971; MS109.001.021.00058 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Spain, 1971; MS109.001.021.00059 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Stavanger and North Sea, 1970; MS109.001.021.00060 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Stockholm, Helsinki, Leningrad, 1971; MS109.001.021.00061 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Stockholm, 1970; MS109.001.021.00062 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Stockholm (for Mr. Olin)-cancelled, 1975; MS109.001.021.00063 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Stockholm (Environment Conference)-Amb not going, 1972; MS109.001.021.00064 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Svalbard-cancelled, 1972; MS109.001.021.00065 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Svalbard, 1970; MS109.001.021.00066 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Tromso, 1972; MS109.001.021.00067 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Trondheim, 1972; MS109.001.021.00068 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S., 1970 -- 1971; MS109.001.021.00069 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S., 1972 -- 1973; MS109.001.021.00070 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S.A., 1970; MS109.001.021.00071 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S. and Canada (Fishing Canada July 1-7) and Transfer to Denmark, 1973; MS109.001.021.00072 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S.A., 1972; MS109.001.021.00073 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Paris and U.S.A., 1971 -- 1972; MS109.001.021.00074 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S.-cancelled, 1975; MS109.001.021.00075 (Box 21)
  - Travel: U.S.A., 1974; MS109.001.021.00076 (Box 21)
  - Travel: Venice, Easter, 1973; MS109.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Travel: Wiesbaden, Germany, 1972; MS109.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Travel: Wiesbaden, Heidelberg, and Berlin, 1969; MS109.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Travel: WWF Meeting in Bonn, 1973; MS109.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Travel: Yugoslavia-cancelled, MS109.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Travel: U.S.A., 1974 -- 1975; MS109.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Talbot, MS109.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Talcot-Tarbat, MS109.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tav-Tay, MS109.001.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tea-Tem, MS109.001.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Ter-That, MS109.001.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thay-Thom, MS109.001.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thomas, MS109.001.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thomas-Thompson, MS109.001.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thompson, MS109.001.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thompson, MS109.001.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thorn-Thos, MS109.001.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thyden, MS109.001.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thy-Tibb, MS109.001.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tid-Tim, MS109.001.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Thorsen, Anne, MS109.001.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tin-Tob, MS109.001.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tobique, MS109.001.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tolstoy, MS109.001.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tolstoy, MS109.001.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tom-Top, MS109.001.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tor-Tra, MS109.001.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Train, MS109.001.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Train-Tre, MS109.001.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tres, MS109.001.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tres-Truman, MS109.001.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tron-Tuc, MS109.001.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Tuc-Tyl, MS109.001.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Uda-Ull, MS109.001.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Ull-Uz, MS109.001.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Vae-Van, MS109.001.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Van-Van, MS109.001.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Ven-Ver, MS109.001.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Ver, MS109.001.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vib-Vin, MS109.001.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vir-Vir, MS109.001.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vir-Vir, MS109.001.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vir-Vis, MS109.001.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vis-Vis, MS109.001.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vis-Vis, MS109.001.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Vis-Vol, MS109.001.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Volk-Volk, MS109.001.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Volk-Volk, MS109.001.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Volp-Vot, MS109.001.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence: Von-, MS109.001.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: African Wildlife Leadership Foundation, MS109.001.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: African Wildlife Leadership Foundation, MS109.001.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: African Wildlife Leadership Foundation (Col. Rhea), MS109.001.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: American Committee for International Wildlife Protection Inc., MS109.001.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: American Committee for International Wildlife Protection, MS109.001.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Articles, MS109.001.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Ceylon Wildlife Protection Society, MS109.001.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: East African Wildlife Society, MS109.001.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (Folder 1), MS109.001.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (Folder 2), MS109.001.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (Folder 3), MS109.001.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: North Africa Mission, 1967; MS109.001.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Russian, MS109.001.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: South African Wildlife Foundation, MS109.001.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Survival Service Commission, 1968 -- 1970; MS109.001.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Wildlife Protection Society of Ceylon, MS109.001.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Wildlife Reports, 1964; MS109.001.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Wildlife: Wildlife Trip, 1963; MS109.001.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Denmark, MS109.001.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Denmark, Secretary General Arne Schiotz, MS109.001.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Finland, MS109.001.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Morges, Switzerland (Folder 1), MS109.001.023.00039 (Box 23)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Morges, Switzerland (Folder 2), MS109.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Morges, Switzerland (Folder 3), MS109.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Morges, Switzerland (Folder 4), MS109.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Morges, Switzerland (Folder 5), MS109.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Norway (Folder 1), MS109.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Norway (Folder 2), MS109.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Norway (Folder 3), MS109.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: 1001 Club, A Nature Trust, MS109.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: 1001 Club, Personal Correspondence, MS109.001.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Sri Lanka, MS109.001.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: South Africa, MS109.001.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: United Kingdom, 1963 -- 1970; MS109.001.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: United States of America (Folder 1), MS109.001.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: United States of America (Folder 2), MS109.001.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA-Letters, MS109.001.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA, MS109.001.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA, MS109.001.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA, MS109.001.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA-Letters, MS109.001.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA-Letters, MS109.001.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: USA, MS109.001.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: My Projects, MS109.001.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Projects, MS109.001.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - World Wildlife Fund: Crowe Papers, MS109.001.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence: Wad-Wal, MS109.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wal-Wal, MS109.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wal-Wal, MS109.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wal-Wat, MS109.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: War-War, MS109.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: War-War, MS109.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Warner, MS109.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Warner, MS109.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Warner, MS109.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: War-Wat, MS109.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Web-Wee, MS109.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wehle, MS109.001.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wehle-Weutzel, MS109.001.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wei-Wein, MS109.001.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wein-Wel, MS109.001.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wen-Wer, MS109.001.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wer-Wes, MS109.001.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Weybright, 1953 -- 1958; MS109.001.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Weybright, 1959 -- 1969; MS109.001.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Weybright, 1970 -- 1975; MS109.001.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Weyher, MS109.001.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wha-Whit, MS109.001.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Whit-Wilc, MS109.001.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wilc-Will, MS109.001.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Williams (Folder 1), MS109.001.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Williams (Folder 2), MS109.001.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Williamson-Wilm, MS109.001.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wils-Wins, MS109.001.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: Wint-Wolf, MS109.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Wolves, 1969; MS109.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Won-Wra, MS109.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Wri-Wym, MS109.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Wright, MS109.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Wyatt-Wynkoop, MS109.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Y, MS109.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Z, MS109.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence: Unknown Authors, MS109.001.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1969; MS109.001.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1969 -- 1970; MS109.001.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1970; MS109.001.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1970; MS109.001.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1970; MS109.001.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1970; MS109.001.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1970; MS109.001.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Chronological Embassy Correspondence, Personal, 1971; MS109.001.026.00017 (Box 26)